<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Aesops on Projeto bilíngue</title><link>http://b.neni.dev/aesop/</link><description>Recent content in Aesops on Projeto bilíngue</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>pt-br</language><atom:link href="http://b.neni.dev/aesop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Avaricious and envious</title><link>http://b.neni.dev/aesop/avaricious-and-envious/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://b.neni.dev/aesop/avaricious-and-envious/</guid><description>Two neighbours came before Jupiter and prayed him to grant their hearts' desire. Now the one was full of avarice, and the other eaten up with envy. So to punish them both, Jupiter granted that each might have whatever he wished for himself, but only on condition that his neighbour had twice as much. The Avaricious man prayed to have a room full of gold. No sooner said than done; but all his joy was turned to grief when he found that his neighbour had two rooms full of the precious metal.</description></item><item><title>The ant and the grasshopper</title><link>http://b.neni.dev/aesop/the_ant_and_the_grasshopper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://b.neni.dev/aesop/the_ant_and_the_grasshopper/</guid><description>The ants were spending a fine winter&amp;rsquo;s day drying grain collected in the summertime. A grasshopper, perishing with famine, passed by and earnestly begged for a little food. The Ants inquired of him, &amp;ldquo;Why did you not treasure up food during the summer?&amp;rdquo; He replied, &amp;ldquo;I had not leisure enough. I passed the days in singing.&amp;rdquo; They then said in derision: &amp;ldquo;If you were foolish enough to sing all the summer, you must dance supperless to bed in the winter.</description></item><item><title>The Bald Man and the Fly</title><link>http://b.neni.dev/aesop/the_bald_man_and_the_fly/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://b.neni.dev/aesop/the_bald_man_and_the_fly/</guid><description>There was once a Bald Man who sat down after work on a hot summer’s day. A Fly came up and kept buzzing about his bald pate, and stinging him from time to time. The Man aimed a blow at his little enemy, but—whack—his palm came on his head instead; again the Fly tormented him, but this time the Man was wiser and said:
&amp;ldquo;You will only injure yourself if you take notice of despicable enemies.</description></item></channel></rss>